Education

Berkeley College: Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration

Professional Summary:

Accomplished business development leader with over 15 years of success selling professional services. Exceptional track record of originating new client engagements, cultivating, and driving sales growth. Team player adept at inspiring colleagues and teams to achieve professional goals. Well versed in identifying market trends and client needs.

Contact

Phone

(917) 288-5445

Email

Kindrak@me.com

Kindra Keener

Professional Experience

OVICE President of Business Development

Basis Vectors Private Equity - New York City • 2022-present

- Lead internal and external relationship building activities with Basis Vectors founders, Global SAAS client engagement team of business development and marketing resources to drive growth and revenue development within the portfolio of \$20+M sales pipeline.
- Developing strategic partnerships and closing sales opportunities, winning new Regional and Global business to BV.
- Manage client relationships to support and drive the execution of acquisition and growth strategy.
- Oversee business development budgets, ensuring timely and accurate resources to achieve strategic revenue objectives
- Support the post-close integration of new acquisitions and organic growth initiatives.
- Campaign development via collaboration with marketing team.

Director, Business Development

Mazars USA, LLP - New York City • 2014-2022

- Proven track record of developing a trusted advisor relationship with existing clients, producing \$2.5+M in revenue per year across multiple services and accounts.
- Consistently drove more than \$1M+ in new client revenues while managing the national territory each year.
- Lead a clear process and structure of a high-performing business development team. Defined the sales process, including lead generation, qualification, nurturing, and closing deals. Created a well-structured team with roles and responsibilities clearly defined.
- Executed prospecting plans, including outbound calls, email, and mail campaigns to effectively make direct contact with prospects.
- Created and led partnerships with clients, prospects and referral sources leading to over \$250K donations for Mazars first annual Women of Water Summit in D.C., generating over \$1M+ new client revenues in less than 6 months.
- Participated in speaking engagements, conferences and sales meetings across multiple industries including (Financial Services, Luxury, Technology, Manufacturing, and Infrastructure).

Marketing and Business Development Manager

Grant Thornton - New York City • 2009-2012

- Developed winning sales strategies, exceeded revenue goals by building market presence and identifying and pursuing new business opportunities in line with Grant Thornton LLP industry approach.
- Produced winning proposals in reaction to the sudden shifts in the accounting industry and capital markets.
- Created opportunities through speaking engagements and active participation through committee memberships at industry organizations.
- Shaped and influenced solutions for our clients in connection with their strategic priorities and firm offerings.
- Identified visibility initiatives, e.g. survey, study or index, speech and presentation opportunities.